<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Fortunes>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Yielding</Name>
		<Text>
The universe is united in power.
So too the wise person execute his actions with power and creativity.
Exceptional progress comes by correct persistence.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="earth">
		<Name>Yielding</Name>
		<Text>
The receptive earth is in power. 
The wise person follows the natural path of calmness and correct persistence.
Others may lead while you support their goals.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Confusion</Name>
		<Text>
Thunderclouds indicate profound disquiet.
Undertake no distant goal, but organize support.
Concern yourself with the problems of the moment.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="water">
		<Name>Inexperience</Name>
		<Text>
As spring water collects at the base of the quiet mountain, 
the enlightened person finds his level through learning,
decisiveness, and correct persistence.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Waiting</Name>
		<Text>
Clouds of anxietyrise. 
Do not be anxious, but wait with confidence.
The moment will arrive when correct persistence brings progress.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="water">
		<Name>Conflict</Name>
		<Text>
Heaven and water, strength and profundity, conflict.
Avoid confrontation. 
Yield with caution. persist not against obstacles.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="water">
		<Name>Cooperation</Name>
		<Text>
The receptive earth holds the water and the wise person will 
find strength in the company of many fellows. 
With leadership there will be correct persistence and good fortune.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="earth">
		<Name>Unity</Name>
		<Text>
The receptive earth beneath. with profundity above,
indicates the need for unity and collective awareness of the goal.
Do not procrastinate. 
Join with others and return to the plan.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Restraint</Name>
		<Text>
The winds of gradual change supported by the strength of Heaven 
shows that restraint brings progress and satisfaction. 
Make minor changes and conceal all actions.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="lake">
		<Name>Correct conduct</Name>
		<Text>
The excessive beneath the strong above. 
Discriminate between the inferior achieve and superior progress.
Change gives way to stability.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Prosperity</Name>
		<Text>
The strength of Heaven mingles with the receptive earth. 
The wise leader benefits from this harmony. 
Good fortune approaches.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="earth">
		<Name>Stagnation</Name>
		<Text>
The strong and the receptive do not meet.
Strong persons give way to the inferior. 
The enlightened person remains reserved to avoid misfortune. 
No advantage in persistence.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="fire">
		<Name>Community</Name>
		<Text>
Strength of heaven, dependence of fire. 
Recognize the dependence of all upon their fellows. 
The wiseperson seeks the collective flow to gain advantage.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Sovereignty</Name>
		<Text>
The strength of heaven holds a fiery intelligence,
the maker of anenlightened ruler. 
Resist evil, exalt good.
Proper Leadership brings great progress.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Moderation</Name>
		<Text>
The tranquil mountainamid the receptive earth indicates great progress
through the reduction of excess. Progress comes by equality of extremes.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="earth">
		<Name>Harmony</Name>
		<Text>
From the receptive earth comes the loud thunder.
So from harmony with supporters does the wise person gain advantage.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Flexibility</Name>
		<Text>
In the midst of excess growth and persistence produces progress.
The enlightened person adapts and leads the way from darkness to comfort.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="wind">
		<Name>Repair</Name>
		<Text>
Winds of gradual change wear away the mountain.
Cultivate action in others to bring about repair and great progress. 
If starting meditate on the future.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="lake">
		<Name>Promotion</Name>
		<Text>
The earth above reflects in the lake beneath. 
So is the enlightened person willing to teach and learn from others.
Progress comes through persistence.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="earth">
		<Name>Contemplation</Name>
		<Text>
As the wind moves over the earth so too the rulers of old travelled the world. 
They visited its regions and contemplated its many cultures.
Explore new ideas.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Reform</Name>
		<Text>
The turbulence of thunder and lightning indicates the need for change. 
Achieve progress through reform.
Administer justice.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="fire">
		<Name>Serenity</Name>
		<Text>
Illumination reveals the foot of the immovable mountain. 
So the wise person perceives and avoids disputes. 
No progress except in small matters.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="earth">
		<Name>Deterioration</Name>
		<Text>
The weak earth cannot support the mountain.
The realm deteriorates.
Enlightened people stabilize their lives through generosity toward the needy
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Repetition</Name>
		<Text>
The beginning of a new cycle shows that repetition brings new progress toward a goal.
Friends return. 
The repeating cycle is part of the Way.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Spontaneity</Name>
		<Text>
Strength above and activity below indicates an alignment with a natural state. 
Act with persistence and inspiration but without a true goal.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Potential</Name>
		<Text>
The strength of the Heavens comes from within the mountain.
The enlightened person studies the past's wisdom to develops his own character.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Nurturing</Name>
		<Text>
Energy stirs beneath immobility. 
Support goals that are above question. but be cautious in expression and avoid the negative. 
Correct persistence brings one good fortune.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="wind">
		<Name>Imminent change</Name>
		<Text>
The enlightened person withdraws from the world to progress toward an independent goal. 
Stress is imminent.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="water">
		<Name>Danger</Name>
		<Text>
Profundity produces difficulty. 
The wise person learns confidence through danger. 
Remain calm in mind keep all actions virtuous.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="fire">
		<Name>Enlightened intelligence</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligence shines above and below. 
The enlightened person cultivates intelligence and gains progress through correct persistence. 
Align yourself with goals that bring enlightenment.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Attraction</Name>
		<Text>
Tranquility combined with excess produces pleasure. 
Marriage brings good fortune.
Accept others and act openly. 
All change is imminent.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="wind">
		<Name>Continuity</Name>
		<Text>
Activity and change teach well the value of endurance. 
Stand firm and move with persistence toward a goal.
Freedom from error.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Retreat</Name>
		<Text>
The tranquil mountain remains quiet under Heaven's gaze. 
So does the enlightened person maintain dignity in retreat. 
Persist only in small matters and avoid mean conflict.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Power</Name>
		<Text>
Activity in the light of day. 
The wise person acts within convention and with persistence.
Use influence wisely.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="earth">
		<Name>Progress</Name>
		<Text>
The sun rises above the earth. 
So does the enlightened person reveal virtue. 
Conditions favorable for progress. 
Help others through cleverness and virtue.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="fire">
		<Name>Subtlety</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligence is hidden within the earth. 
Conceal goals, but do not abandon them. 
Trying conditions but correct persistence brings one advantage.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="fire">
		<Name>Family</Name>
		<Text>
Winds of change issue from intelligent action.
The enlightened person acts in an orderly and substantial way.
Faith and loyalty must be nurtuted.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="lake">
		<Name>Contradiction</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligence contradicts excess. 
The enlightened person acts only in small matters. 
Maintain individuality
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Obstacles</Name>
		<Text>
Profound movement meets immobility. 
The enlightened person examines and perfects his own behavior to gain strength.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="water">
		<Name>Liberation</Name>
		<Text>
Rain and thunder indicate profound activity.
The enlightened person finds good fortune in quick action to restore normal conditions. 
Forgive others' faults.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="lake">
		<Name>Decline</Name>
		<Text>
Excess is held by immobility. 
The enlightened person acts with moderation. 
Avoid anger, develop confidence. 
Sacrifice brings good fortune, freedom from error.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Benefit</Name>
		<Text>
Growth brings benefit.
An enlightened person sees the good actions of his fellows. 
Imitate them and correct their mistakes to make progress toward a goal.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="heaven">
		<Name>Resolve</Name>
		<Text>
Excess drawn into Heaven's gaze produces honesty. 
Do not use force but rely on fair judges. 
Know your goal, tell your supporters.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="heaven" Below="wind">
		<Name>Temptation</Name>
		<Text>
Heaven's power makes stronger the wind of change. 
So too a ruler issues commands that become well known. 
Do not create a relationship with powe)ful persons
or ideas. Exert discipline.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="earth">
		<Name>Assembly</Name>
		<Text>
The earth receives excess. 
Unite with others, make sacrifices, and act with correct persistence to achieve a goal.
Act with sincerity, avoid suspicion, and join with a wise leader.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="earth" Below="wind">
		<Name>Advancement</Name>
		<Text>
Gradual change, nourished by the receptive earth, produces a path to virtue. 
The enlightened person persists in small matters to gain fortune. 
Approach leaders without fear.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="water">
		<Name>Adversity</Name>
		<Text>
Excess lacks profundity. 
The enlightened person gains progress through courage. 
Adversity needs risks to achieve fortune. 
Speaking alone is uneffective.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="wind">
		<Name>Insight</Name>
		<Text>
Profound penetration and change. 
Truth is never exhausted, yet never the same. 
The enlightened person gains insight into truth and assists others to achieve it. 
If the truth is not heeded, bad fortune follows.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="fire">
		<Name>Change</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligent consciousness amid excess produces change. 
The enlightened person appreciates past experience and present opportunity. 
Confidence and progress only after change is past.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="wind">
		<Name>Order</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligence combined with penetration makes progress and good fortune. 
The wise person aligns himself with the established order.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="thunder">
		<Name>Shock</Name>
		<Text>
Repeated activity produces sudden surprise and fear. 
The enlightened person seeks to improve himself and take advantage of the unpredictable.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="mountain" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Meditation</Name>
		<Text>
Tranquility upon tranquility. 
The enlightened person turns his back upon the larger situation and loses self awareness. 
Should he not notice anyone else, there is no error
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Development</Name>
		<Text>
Penetrating change moves the immobile mountain. 
The enlightened person improves life through good conduct and correct persistence. 
Marriage brings good fortune.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="lake">
		<Name>Passivity</Name>
		<Text>
Action above, excess below. 
The enlightened person in current difficulty takes no action but considers the near future. 
Seek no goal.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="fire">
		<Name>Peaking intelligence</Name>
		<Text>
Intelligence combined with activity. 
This is the zenith of achievement. 
The enlightened person trusts his own judgment and makes progress. 
Do not fear decline, but shine like the sun.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Travel</Name>
		<Text>
Illumination upont he quiet mountain makes conditions favorable for travel. 
The wise person is clear-minded and not detained by disputes.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="wind">
		<Name>Influence</Name>
		<Text>
Penetrating change above and be low. 
The enlightened person acts gradually and only toward small goals.
Wait and consider larger perspectives.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="lake" Below="lake">
		<Name>Encouragement</Name>
		<Text>
Openness and excess above and be low. 
The wise person exchanges ideas with others to find cooperation. 
Progress and advantage in correct persistence.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="water">
		<Name>Reunion</Name>
		<Text>
Gradual change above the profound water.
Rulers meet with their subordinates. 
Advantage in cooperation, correct persistence, and the company offellows.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="lake">
		<Name>Limitation</Name>
		<Text>
Profundity is held in check by excess. 
The wise person develops sound restraints and decides proper conduct.
Extreme limitation, though, is no virtue.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="wind" Below="lake">
		<Name>Understanding</Name>
		<Text>
Penetrating change above the open lake.
From a distance the wise person gains understanding. 
Moderate disputes and must avoid rigidity.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="thunder" Below="mountain">
		<Name>Attention to detail</Name>
		<Text>
As the mountain remains tranquil in activity, so the wise person conducts himself with dignity and control. 
Be remorseful in losses and frugal in expenses.
When birdsflytoo high, none hear their song.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="water" Below="fire">
		<Name>Precaution</Name>
		<Text>
In consciousness is bred profound difficulty. 
The enlightened person defends against forthcoming adversity. 
Progress only in small matters.
Confusion is imminent.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
	<Fortune Above="fire" Below="water">
		<Name>Vigilance</Name>
		<Text>
Consciousness above the difficult water. 
The wise person attends his position and progress carefully. 
Progress with great vigilance.
		</Text>
	</Fortune>
</Fortunes>
